Hi, welcome to the AnimationTech channel where we will be looking at the technical side of animation
in video game mainly by re-implementing old animation paper that we released a long time ago
up to papers that were actually more recent and we will re-implement them inside of Python
so we could have an easy visualization of what those papers were about. We will also probably
talk a bit about physics and also the mathematics behind animations and physics in video games.
My name is Jérôme Perth and I'm an animation technical director for the past 20 years in
the game industry. I've been working mainly into designing animation pipeline, writing tools,
or writing engine code about animations. And I hope this channel will be of an interest for you
and if you want to make sure that they're here about all the videos I would be releasing
frequently, I would try to be constant in my release. I would say probably one a month or
something like that. Make sure that you hit the subscribe button and see you in the next video.